export default [
{
  concept: {
     uid: "2",
     name: "Red Herring",
     conceptName: "Red Herring",
     standard: "4.1g. Red Herring"
   },
 	answer: "We [wanted] to get ice cream [after] [our] soccer game, but then the weather suddenly turned [too] cold.",
 	prompt: "We [wanted] to get ice cream [after] [our] soccer game, but then the weather suddenly turned [too] cold."
},
{
  concept: {
   uid: "4",
   name: "Prepositions",
   conceptName: "Prepositions",
   standard: "Prepositions"
  },
  answer: "[Every year,] I spend a week [staying] {with} my cousins.",
  prompt: "[Every year,] I spend a week [staying] {for} my cousins.",
  needsFixing: true
},
{
 concept: {
   uid: "5",
   name: "Demonstratives ",
   conceptName: "Demonstratives ",
   standard: "Demonstratives"
  },
  answer: "{These} keys [keep] jingling [in] my pocket.",
 	prompt: "{Those} keys [keep] jingling [in] my pocket.",
  needsFixing: true
},
{
  concept: {
    uid: "6",
    name: "Irregular Past Tense Verbs ",
    conceptName: "Irregular Past Tense Verbs ",
    standard: "Irregular Past Tense Verbs "
  },
  answer: "[Last week,] James {broke} his [mother’s] favorite mug.",
  prompt: "[Last week,] James {break} his [mother’s] favorite mug.",
  needsFixing: true
},
{
  concept: {
     uid: "7",
     name: "Reflexive Pronouns ",
     conceptName: "Reflexive Pronouns ",
     standard: "Reflexive Pronouns "
   },
  answer: "The beavers [built] {themselves} a dam for their [baby beavers].",
  prompt: "The beavers [built] {them} a dam for their [baby beavers].",
  needsFixing: true

},
{
  concept: {
   uid: "8",
   name: "Adjectives to Adverbs ",
   conceptName: "Adjectives to Adverbs",
   standard: "Adjectives to Adverbs"
 },
  answer: "She {quickly} finished [her] homework [during] recess.",
 	prompt: "She {quick} finished [her] homework [during] recess.",
  needsFixing: true
},
{
  concept: {
     uid: "9",
     name: "Comparative Adjectives",
     conceptName: "Comparative Adjectives",
     standard: "Comparative Adjectives"
   },
   answer: "[That] pot is {blacker} [than] the kettle.",
   prompt: "[That] pot is {black} [than] the kettle.",
   needsFixing: true
},
{
  concept: {
   uid: "10",
   name: "Possessive Nouns",
   conceptName: "Possessive Nouns",
   standard: "Possessive Nouns"
 },
  answer: "The {teacher’s} pencil [fell] [onto] the ground.",
  prompt: "The {teachers} pencil [fell] [onto] the ground.",
  needsFixing: true
},
{
  concept: {
    uid: "9",
    name: "Comparative Adjectives",
    conceptName: "Comparative Adjectives",
    standard: "Comparative Adjectives"
  },
  answer: "[He believes] that cereal is {best} [with] milk.",
  prompt: "[He believes] that cereal is {goodest} [with] milk.",
  needsFixing: true
},
{
  concept: {
    uid: "11",
    name: "Loose, Lose",
    conceptName: "Loose, Lose",
    standard: "Loose, Lose"
  },
  answer: "Please [be careful] that you don’t {lose} [your keys]!",
  prompt: "Please [be careful] that you don’t {loose} [your keys]!",
  needsFixing: true
},
{
  concept: {
    uid: "12",
    name: "Relative Pronouns",
    conceptName: "Relative Pronouns",
    standard: "Relative Pronouns"
  },
  answer: "[I am looking] for my mother, {who} passed by [this] store [a few minutes ago].",
  prompt: "[I am looking] for my mother, {that} passed by [this] store [a few minutes ago].",
  needsFixing: true
},
{
  concept: {
    uid: "13",
    name: "Finally, Finely",
    conceptName: "Finally, Finely",
    standard: "Finally, Finely"
  },
  answer: "The [library’s] books were so {finely} organized [by the librarians].",
  prompt: "The [library’s] books were so {finally} organized [by the librarians].",
  needsFixing: true
}
]
